- 안녕?
- 왔어?
So what happened?
Did a forest tick you off?
뭐야?
나무가 너한테 죄졌냐?
우편물 보관할 데가
마땅치 않아서
We always say
we need a place for the mail.
근데?
I started building one. But then
I decided to take it to the next step.
그걸 만들려다가
더 근사한 걸
만들기로 한 거지
You're building a post office?
우체국이라도 짓게?
종합 장식장을 만들어서
한 칸을 편지함으로 쓸 거야
No, an entertainment unit,
with a built-in mail cubby.
It's a one-day job, max.
- 길게 잡아 하루면 끝나
- 좋아
My word, those are snug!
바지 터지겠다!
작업복이야
These are my old work pants.
Sergio Valente.
서지오 발렌테!
Power saw kind of got away
from me there.
전기톱을 놓치는 바람에
The One With Frank Jr.
Hey, Pheebs.
Any sign of your brother?
피비!
- 동생 아직 안 왔어?
- 걘 맨날 늦거든
No, but he's always late.
-I thought you only met him once.
-I did.
- 한 번밖에 못 봤다며?
- 맞아
I think it sounds big sister-y,
"Frank's always late."
'걘 맨날 늦어'하니까
제법 누나답지?
Well, relax. He'll be here.
걱정 마, 오겠지
I know.
I'm just nervous.
긴장돼서 그래
It's just, Mom's dead,
don't talk to my sister...
엄만 돌아가셔, 언니랑은 말도
안해, 할머닌 잠만 주무시니까
...Grandma's been sleeping
a lot lately.
It's just the "last-desperate-
chance-to-have-a-family" kind of thing.
가족애를 느낄
마지막 기회야
같이 기다려줘서 고마워
You're sweet to wait with me.
사실은 건터가
컵 가지고 들어오랬거든
Actually, Gunther sent me. You're not
allowed to have cups out here.
Does anyone else think
David Copperfield's cute?
데이비드 카퍼필드가
섹시한 것 같아?
아니, 근데 그 사람은
너더러 죽여준대
No. But he told me he thinks
you're a fox.
All right. Janice likes him.
사실은 제니스가 좋아해
얼마나 좋아하는지
In fact, she likes him so much,
she put him on her "freebie" list.
'같자스 리스트'에도
올려놨다니까
Her what?
뭔 리스트?
We have a deal where we each pick five
celebrities we could sleep with...
같이 자고 싶은 스타
5명을 각자 정했거든
...and the other one can't get mad.
그 사람들하곤
용납되는 거야
건전한 관계의 핵심이지
The heart of every
healthy relationship:
Honesty, respect
and sex with celebrities.
솔직함, 존중, 스타와의
섹스는 말야
네 리스트엔 누가 있는데?
So who's on your list?
IKim Basinger...
킴 베이싱어, 신디 크로포드
할리 베리, 야스민 블리스
... Cindy Crawford, Halle Berry...
...Yasmine Bleeth...
탁월해
그리고...
제시카 래빗
...and Jessica Rabbit.
그 여잔 만화주인공이고
너랑 과가 다르지
You do realize that she is a cartoon,
and way out of your league?
내가 제시카 눈을 튀어나오게
할 수 있나 궁금했을 뿐이야
I know. I just wonder if I could
get her eyes to pop out of her head.
Who would yours be?
넌 누구로 할 거야?
First, I need a boyfriend.
Then I can have a list.
애인 먼저 만들고
리스트 만들 거야
It's just a game, Mon.
깐깐하긴
Rach, how about you?
레이첼, 너는?
글쎄...
I don't know. I guess Chris
O'Donnell, John F. IKennedy Jr...
크리스 오도넬
존 F. 케네디 2세
... Daniel Day-Lewis, Sting
and Parker Stevenson.
다니엘 데이 루이스, 스팅,
파커 스티븐슨
Spiderman?
스파이더맨?
Hardy Boy.
하디 보이!
-Peter Parker.
-Thank you.
- 피터 파커지
- 고마워
What about you, honey?
Who'd be on your list?
그럼 자기는
누굴 넣을 거야?
그런 문제는 신중하게
검토해야 돼
That kind of thing
requires some serious thought.
First, I'd divide my prospective
candidates into categories.
우선 예상 후보들을
종류 별로 나눠야지
주접이야
What a geek!
Everybody, this is Frank!
My half brother, Frank!
얘들아, 얘가 내 이복동생
프랭크야
This is everybody.
인사들 해
- 이쪽은 로스
- 안녕?
-This is Ross.
-How are you?
챈들러
조이
This is Monica.
저긴 모니카
And this is Rachel.
이쪽은 레이첼
I'm gonna get coffee for us.
커피 가져올게
Hey, how do you guys get
anything done?
다들 재주도 좋네요
We don't, really.
재주는 무슨?
Do you guys have big plans?
계획 빠방하게 세웠겠다
Oh, yeah. We're gonna connect
and bond and everything.
별 건 아니고 서먹한 거
없애고 친해져 보려구
타임즈 광장에 가서
닌자 스타를 살 거예요
I thought we could go down to Times
Square and pick up some ninja stars.
또 친구 녀석이 창녀 사진도
찍어오랬어요
My friend, Larry, he wants me
to take a picture of a hooker.
그 좋은 걸 우린 왜 몰랐지?
We really don't take advantage
of living in the city.
Oh, sorry. Did I get you?
미안! 닿았어?
닿지야 않았지!
No, you didn't "get" me!
전기 드릴인데
닿았다간 벌써 죽었게?
It's an electric drill!
You "get" me, you kill me!
Calm down!
Do you want this unit or not?
이게 나만 좋자고 하는 거냐?
I do not want this unit!
난 필요 없어!
You should've told me before.
I'm not a mind reader.
진작 말했어야지
내가 알았냐?
And we're out of beer.
I'm going to Monica's.
맥주가 떨어졌네
모니카네 간다
맘대로 해
Fine!
안녕?
오늘 패션 컨셉은
1982년이야?
Where you heading in those pants?
1982?
I saw down at the hardware store, they
got those designer tiles on sale...
아까 철물점 갔더니
욕실 타일 싸게 팔던데
...if you wanna redo
your bathroom floor.
새로 깔 생각 없어?
What's wrong with my bathroom floor?
뭐하러 다시 깔아?
Nothing. It's just old and dingy,
that's all.
오래 돼서 꼬질꼬질하잖아
I highly doubt that.
- 말도 안돼
- 그럴까?
If you move your hamper...
이걸 한번 치워볼까?
저게 원래 색깔이야
...you see how
the tile used to be.
그래
I can't live like this!
What are we gonna do?
이렇게는 못 살아
어떻게 해야 되니?
진정해, 들고 있어
기술자께서 보여줄게
Relax. Here, hold this.
This old stuff comes right up.
I'll show you.
A little more than I wanted to see.
정말 보기 민망하다
저것 봐!
꼼꼼히도 발라놨네
Look at that!
Every inch of this is glued down!
It'd take forever to pry this up.
You should just leave it.
다 뜯다간 늙어죽겠군
그냥 둬야겠다
I can't leave it! You gouged
a hole in my dingy floor!
그냥 두라니?
꼬질꼬질한데
구멍까지 내놓고?
There. There you go.
어때? 괜찮지?
Yeah, that's nice.
저것보단 네 살 벗겨서
바르는 게 낫지 않겠어?
We can put it back there after the
surgeons remove it from your colon!
왜?
I know what I wanted to ask you.
Can you roll your tongue?
물어볼 거 생각났어
너 혀 말기 돼?
Because I can and my mom couldn't.
난 되는데 엄마는 못 하셨거든
아빠한테 물려받은 건가 해서
And I figured that was
something I got from our dad.
- 이런 거 말야?
- 맞아, 너도 되는구나
Well, wait, you mean like this?
Yeah, you can do it too. Yeah.
You're not doing it.
안되는구만
Oh, right. Okay.
Yeah, my mom could and I can't.
맞다! 엄만 되고
난 안 됐어
공통점이 아니었네
We don't have that.
When's your birthday?
- 생일이 언제야?
- 2월 16일
February 16th.
I know a guy who's the 18th.
친구 생일은 18일인데
That's close.
거의 같네
When's yours?
- 네 생일은?
- 10월 25일
October 25th.
That's the same month as Halloween.
할로윈이랑 같은 달이네
So what kind of things
do you like to do at home?
집에 있을 땐 주로 뭐해?
Melt stuff.
녹이는 일
세 명은 정했다
-Okay, I've got three of my five.
-Three of your five what?
무슨 세 명?
같이 자고 싶은
스타 말이야
Celebrities I'm allowed to sleep with.
세상에!
그걸 아직까지 고민해?
God, you're giving this
a lot of thought.
어렵다구
두 명은 아직 못 정했어
Hey, it's hard, okay?
I only have two spots left.
All right. Who you got it
narrowed down to?
누가 유력한데?
Elizabeth Hurley.
엘리자베스 헐리
Very attractive.
매력 있지
Forgiving.
이해심도 많고
Susan Sarandon.
수잔 서랜든
You know what? She's too political.
수잔은 너무 정치적이야
불우이웃 돕기부터 하고
오라고 할걸?
She'd probably make you donate
four cans of food first.
And lsabella Rossellini.
그리고...
이자벨라 로셀리니
Very hot. Very sexy.
화끈하고 섹시하지
근데...
But she's too international.
She's never gonna be around.
국제적인 스타라서
마주칠 일도 없을 거라구
-So?
-So you gotta play the odds.
그래서?
제외시켜야지, 이 나라에
사는 사람 중에서 고르라구
Pick somebody who's gonna be
in the country all the time.
Yeah. Because that's why you won't
get lsabella Rossellini. Geography.
그래서 이자벨라 로셀리니는
지역적 장벽 때문에 빼겠다?
Okay. So by "melting"
you meant melting.
'녹이는 일'이란 게
이거였어?
응
- 이것도 예술이니?
- 예술도 녹일 수 있지
So is it, like, art?
Yeah, you can melt art.
Hey, can I use your phone?
전화 좀 써도 돼?
그럼!
엄마한테 전화하게?
-Sure. You want to call your mom?
-No, I want to melt it.
아니, 녹이려고
Oh. Well, not right now.
그럼 나중에 써
I'm gonna go to bed. The fumes
are giving me a headache. So....
난 그만 자야겠어
냄새 땜에 어지러워서
그렇게 해
Good night, "bro."
잘 자, 동생
잘 자
Good night.
Here.
혹시 모르니까
Just in case.
Oh, excellent!
멋진걸!
-What kind of karate is that?
-No kind.
저건 무슨 가라데야?
뭔 놈의 가라데?
He just makes it up.
되는대로 하는 거야
-How's it going with you guys?
-So far it kind of blows.
둘이 잘 지내?
돌아버릴 것 같아
I don't know, I just thought
he'd feel more like a brother.
남매니까 금방
친해질 줄 알았지
너랑 로스처럼
친하고 아껴주고...
Like you and Ross.
Close and connected and....
We're close now.
You wouldn't believe the years...
지금이야 그렇지만
몇 년 전만 해도
...of noogies, and wedgies, and flying
wedgies, and atomic wedgies and....
물고 뜯고 차고 던지고
난리도 아니었어
That's when the waistband
goes over your head.
그러다 보면 허리끈이
이렇게 올라가기도 해
그림자 놀이 때문에
열도 많이 받았지
We drove each other crazy
playing the shadow game.
-How do you play the shadow game?
- 그림자 게임이 뭔데?
-I just asked you.
- 내가 물었잖아
I don't have time for this.
이제 그만하자
이렇게 하는 거야
-That is what the game is.
-You just gave up really quickly.
그만하쟀다고
바로 관두네
-Seen Joey?
-What's the matter?
- 조이 못 봤어?
- 왜 그래?
Oh, just this!
이것 좀 봐!
It's my fault, really, because the
couch is where we keep the varnish.
따지고 보면 소파에 니스
놔둔 거 잊은 내 탓이지
Somebody wanna hand me
one of those tiles?
누구 와서 타일 좀 집어줘
-What's going on?
-He's retiling my floor.
- 뭐야?
- 타일 깔아주고 있어
어이, 아저씨!
Spackle boy!
-Get up!
-You started this, you'll finish it!
일어나!
- 벌여놨으면 끝장을 봐야지
- 내 게 먼저야
He started mine first!
Build the unit, Cinderellie
Lay the tile, Cinderellie
장식장 만들어, 신데렐라
타일 깔아야지, 신데렐라
와! 문어 엄청 크다
Big octopus.
정말!
여보세요?
Oh, my God! I totally forgot!
깜빡 잊을 뻔했잖아!
Well, can't someone else do it?
대신 할 사람 없어?
But I have company.
누가 와있어서 그래
Look, that's all right.
I'll come in.
알았어, 갈게
그래
I'm sorry,
but I have to go into work.
프랭크, 미안한데
일하러 가야 돼
It's one of my regulars who's
insisting that I do him, so....
단골 손님인데
굳이 날 찾는대
무슨 일 하는데?
Hey, what kind of work do you do?
I'm a masseuse.
안마사야
안마해주는 사람 말야
I give people massages and stuff.
You work at one of
those massage parlors?
그럼 안마시술소에서 일해?
Well, you know, we don't call it that.
But, yeah.
명칭은 좀 다르지만
대충 맞아
That's wild.
No, I had no idea.
정말 몰랐어
괜찮아
Alrighty.
I'll be back in a little bit.
금방 올 테지만...
같이 갈래?
Unless you want to come with me.
You mean, like, watch?
구경하란 말야?
No. No, you can get one yourself.
It'll be on the house.
아니, 너도 하면 되잖아
공짜로 해줄게
What are big sisters for?
누나 좋다는 게 뭐니?
Well, I don't think this. You know?
난 됐어
No. No, no.
I wouldn't do you myself.
내가 해줄 건 아냐
좀 이상하잖아
I mean, that would be weird.
다른 애 구해줄게
너무 재밌겠다
I'll get one of the
other girls to do it.
This is so much fun!
Are you excited?
- 기대되지?
- 응
모니카랑 레이첼도
거기서 일해?
Hey, do Monica and Rachel work there?
It's beautiful!
멋져!
It's like the first bathroom
floor there ever was!
이렇게 멋진
욕실 바닥은 처음 봐
What are you going in there for?
뭐하시려고?
큰 건 아냐
You want, like, a number?
- 안녕
- 고마워
Hi. Bye.
Okay. I'm done with my choices.
이제 다 골랐어
최종 리스트야
These are final.
-Well, it's about time.
-Yeah. Very official.
- 오래도 걸렸네
- 신경 좀 썼는데
Oh, yeah. Well, you know, Chandler
printed it up on his computer.
챈들러가 프린터로 뽑아줬어
코팅은 누가 했는데?
And who laminated it?
That was me.
내가 했지
좀 볼까?
All right, let me see.
"Uma Thurman, Winona Ryder,
Elizabeth Hurley...
우마 써먼, 위노나 라이더,
엘리자베스 헐리, 미셸 파이퍼
... Michelle Pfeiffer...
... Dorothy Hamill"?
도로시 해밀?
내 맘이야
Hey, it's my list!
그 여잔 빙판에서만
쌩쌩 도는 거 알지?
You do realize she only spins
like that on ice?
기적의 약손
-What's going on?
-She broke my arm!
- 무슨 일이야?
- 팔 부러지겠어
내 엉덩이를 만졌어
-He touched my fanny.
-She touched mine first!
- 내 걸 먼저 만졌다구
- 내 일이니까
That's my job!
So what's the deal? I can have sex
with you but I can't touch you?
이봐요, 섹스하면서
만지지도 못한단 말예요?
뭐?
섹스를 하다니?
-You can't have sex with her!
-Did you think I was a hooker?
내가 창녀인 줄 알았어?
다 알고 왔어요
난 경찰도 아닌데 어때요?
No, okay. I know. You're a masseuse.
It's cool. I'm not a cop!
재스민, 내 손님한테
잠깐 기다리시라고 전해줘
Ask Mr. Wiffler if he
can wait for five minutes.
Fine.
알았어
너 딱 걸렸어
I don't like you.
So that's what you thought I did?
God!
내가 그런 줄
알았단 말이지?
That's not what I do!
어떻게 그럴 수가!
Wait, that's not what you do?
- 그게 아니란 말야?
- 당연하지!
No!
Why would you think that?
- 왜 그렇게 생각했어?
- 모르겠어
I don't know. This is the city,
you know? I just....
여긴 대도시고...
난 그냥...
I mean...
... I don't know.
나도 몰라
Whatever. It's the perfect end
to the perfect weekend anyway.
됐어, 이번 주말은
정말이지 끝내준다
Oh, wait.
저기... 맞아
끝내줬어
No, you're right.
No, it was perfect.
내가 망쳐놓긴 했지만 말야
I can't believe
I screwed it up so bad.
You thought it was perfect?
진짜 그렇게 생각해?
물론 아주 끝내준 건 아니지만
되게 좋았어
Well, no, maybe it wasn't perfect...
... but you know, it was pretty cool,
you know?
Because we had all those
great talks, you know?
터놓고 대화도 나눴고...
어떤 부분이 특히 좋았는데?
Which ones in particular
were great for you?
Well, you know, about
the tongue thing, you know?
혀 말기도 좋았고
And how I told you about
my likes and my dislikes.
내가 좋아하는 것과
싫어하는 것도 얘기했지
안 녹는 물건을 내가
얼마나 싫어하는지 말했잖아
How I like to melt stuff, and how
I dislike stuff that doesn't melt.
Right. Okay.
맞아
누나니까 솔직하게
말하고 싶었던 거야
I feel like I can really talk to you
because you're my sister, you know?
Yeah. I guess I do.
나도 그래
근데 내가 실수해서
누나가 열 받았지
And then I go feel your friend up
and make you mad at me.
그 정도는 아니었어
Well, I wasn't hopping mad,
you know?
You hopped a little bit.
열 받았잖아
Yeah, I'm really sorry.
You know, I'm really....
암튼 정말 미안해
Okay.
괜찮아
Well, this is my favorite part
of the weekend. Right now. This.
이번 주말 중 지금
이 순간이 제일 좋아
- 지금이?
- 응
This?
Oh, come on. We went to Times Square.
타임즈 광장에도 가고
닌자 스타스까지 샀는데도?
We found ninja stars. I almost
get my arm broken by a hooker
난 오늘 창녀한테 팔을...
She's not a hooker.
창녀 아니래두
When I tell my friends about her,
she will be.
친구들한텐 창녀라고
자랑할 텐데 뭐
셋에 들어올려
On 3!
1, 2
하나, 둘...
Why don't we just go on 2?
- 둘에 올리면 안돼?
- 왜?
Why 2?
더 빠르잖아
Because it's faster.
그 얘기할 동안
셋을 네 번은 셌겠다
I could've counted to 3 four times
without all the "2" talk.
-All right, but in the future
-Heavy thing! Not getting lighter!
- 알았어, 다음부턴...
- 됐어
- 무거워 죽겠단 말야
- 센다
1, 2
하나, 둘...
So we are going with two?
둘에 올려?
A good job, Joe.
훌륭해, 조이
Wow.
It's big.
좀 크군
그래, 너무 커서
문이 작아 보인다
So big it actually makes
our doors look smaller.
Maybe my ruler's wrong.
- 자가 이상해서 그래
- 안 이상한 자가 있을까?
Maybe all the rulers are wrong.
It's not that bad. So it blocks a
little of your door, a little of mine.
쓸 만한데 뭐, 네 문이랑
내 문 좀 가린다고 그래?
I got a better idea.
좋은 수가 있다
내 문은 안 가리고
네 문만 더 가리는 거야
How about it blocks none of my door,
and a lot of your door?
깜빡했는데
그 쪽 아직 안 말랐어
Listen, before I forget,
that side is still wet.
손님,
주문하신 그대로예요
Let me just see
if I've got this right.
So this is a half-caf, double-tall,
easy hazelnut...
저카페인, 큰 컵에
연한 헤이즐넛
무지방, 거품 없이, 생크림,
뜨거운 우유 듬뿍 맞죠?
... nonfat, no foam, with whip,
extra-hot latte, right?
맛있게 드세요
Okay. Great.
미친놈!
You freak.
Thank you.
고마워요
A coffee to go, please.
커피 한잔 주세요
Isabella Rossellini!
이자벨라 로셀리니야!
정말?
Are you serious? Oh, my God!
세상에!
이럴 줄 알았으면
리스트에 넣는 건데
Damn! I cannot believe
I took her off my list!
Why? Because otherwise
you'd go for it?
왜? 그랬으면
시도라도 해보게?
Yeah, maybe.
그럴 수도 있지
웃기시네
You lie.
You don't think I'd go up to her?
못 할 것 같아?
나한테도 10년씩
걸렸는데 하물며!
It took you 10 years to finally admit
you liked me.
내 리스트를 코팅해놓은 걸
다행으로 생각해
Yeah? Well, missy, you better be glad
that list is laminated.
You know what, honey? You go ahead.
We'll call her an alternate.
그럼 한번 가봐
대타로 쳐줄 테니까
- 좋아, 들고 있어
- 그래
Hold my cruller.
Are you really gonna
let him do this?
정말 허락하는 거야?
이자벨라 로셀리니가 약 먹었어?
재밌게 구경이나 하자구
He's about to go hit
on lsabella Rossellini.
I'm just sorry we don't got popcorn.
안녕하세요?
전 로스라고 해요
I'm Ross.
절 모르시겠지만
엄청난 팬이랍니다
You don't know me,
but I'm a big, big fan of yours.
'블루 벨벳' 최고예요!
I mean...
...Blue Velvet.
I was wondering if I could maybe
buy you a cup of coffee.
커피 한잔
대접하고 싶은데요
Or reimburse you for that one.
아니면 찻값 돌려드릴까요?
Aren't you with that girl over there?
여자 친구 아니에요?
그렇긴 한데 괜찮아요
합의를 봤거든요
Well, yeah, kind of.
But that's okay.
We have an understanding.
We each have this list of five famous
people, and you were one of mine.
각자 좋아하는 스타
5명씩을 적었는데
당신은 내 명단에 있기 땜에
같이 자도 괜찮아요
So I'm allowed to sleep with you.
그 만큼 멋지시단 거죠
It's flattering.
I don't know
잠깐만요, 이자벨라
Wait. Wait, lsabella.
Don't dismiss this so fast. This is
a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
평생에 한번 있을까 말까한
기회를 이렇게 버리시게요?
Yeah, for you.
댁한테나 그렇죠
Is that the list?
- 이게 리스트예요?
- 네
-Yes.
-Can I see it?
- 봐도 돼요?
- 아뇨
-Come on.
-But Okay.
- 좀 봐요
- 그래요
I'm not on the list!
난 없군요
But that's not the final draft.
최종 리스트가 아니거든요
It's laminated.
코팅까지 됐는데요
Okay, see, you were on my list.
원래는 리스트에 있었어요
근데 제 친구 챈들러가...
But then my friend, Chandler...
... brought up the point
that you are international.
예리한 지적을 했죠
당신은 국제적인 스타라구요
So I bumped you for Winona Ryder.
Local.
그래서 국내파인
위노나 라이더로 바꿨죠
You know, it's ironic,
because I have a list...
- 참 재밌네요
- 뭐가요?
저도 카페의 미남 손님
리스트를 만들었거든요
...of five goofy coffeehouse guys.
And yesterday, I just bumped you
for that guy over there.
근데 어제 당신을 빼고
저 사람을 넣었어요
그냥 친구나 할까봐
We're just gonna be friends.
You know what?
있잖아
Bet you I could fit in there.
나 저기 들어갈 수 있어
못 한다는 데 5달러 건다
I got five bucks says you can't.
Get out your checkbook, mister.
수표책이나 준비해둬
Oh, I think I have the cash.
현금은 안돼?
네가 졌어
You are dog, man!
I totally fit!
아주 딱 맞아
Yeah. You got me.
그래, 축하해
I'm out five big ones.
5달러 짜리로 줄게
There you go.
자, 받아
Thank you.
고마워
짜잔!
Oh, well, hello, Mr. Lincoln!
안녕하세요, 링컨 씨?
Better luck next time, buddy!
다음엔 운이 따라주겠지
And the drinks are on me!
대신 한잔 쏠게